This here is
a radon test kit.
Okay, l'll be
putting them everywhere.
And please don't
throw these out.
This is a radon test kit.
Please don't
throw these out.
You'll see them
all over the office.
Toby has been leaving
radon kits everywhere
like he owns the place.
The first time I threw
mine away, I thought
it was an ant trap.
But I figured I'd
rather Iive with ants
than with this
creepy little disk.
The second time,
I thought it was
one of those,
you know,
the things you turn over
and it moos like a cow thing,
but upon closer examination
it was another ant trap,
so I threw it away.
And the third time,
I did it out of spite.
(MAKlNG FARTlNG NOlSES)
Come on, Michael,
you're interrupting.
You're kidding me! God !
You say radon is
silent but deadly
and then you expect me
not to make farting noises
with my mouth?
What is this?
Please sit down.
You know what,
we're not gonna die
of radon,
we're gonna die of boredom.
Yeah.
MlCHAEL: Right?
And if l had a gun
with two bullets,
and l was in a room
with Hitler,
Bin Laden and Toby,
l would shoot Toby twice.
(ALL MUTTERlNG)
Okay, all right.
You were being really funny
and then you went too far.
l would kill Bin Laden
and then Toby.
No. That's still. . .
Okay, geniuses,
how would you do it?
Curve the bullet
like in my favorite
James McAvoy film Wanted.
All that does is help you
shoot around things.
What does Bin Laden. . .
ls there
a curtain rod in the room?
MlCHAEL: l don't know.
How about
make-believe land has
anything you want?
Stanley, please,
this is serious.
ls this the thing
where they use an icicle
so there's no evidence?
Yes, we should stab Toby
through the heart
with an icicle.
(GROANS) Come on,
the whole two bullet thing
is a red herring.
Here's how you do it.
You line them all up,
you take one bullet,
shoot them all
through the throat
at the same time.
Watch this.
Phyllis, you're Hitler,
come up here.
Toby, you're Toby.
Andy, you're Bin Laden.
Line up.
TOBY: l don't want to do this.
DWlGHT: Throats together.
Toby, just do it!
Toby, come on.
God.
Ready, one bullet and. . .
Boom !
(lMlTATlNG BULLET lMPACT)
ANDY: Yeah, that works.
lt worked !
What flavors did you get?
lt's so exciting, Pam.
The Eagles are doing
a theme of ice creams
in honor of turning 60.
"Despera-Dough,
Witchy-Womanilla."
Why do they do this?
Do you want me to
go back to the store?
No, no, no, it's fine.
l was just commenting.
We got to get these out,
open them up.
Okay.
This is all for Michael.
Turns out his
girlfriend was married.
PAM: Yeah,
and when MichaeI
gets a broken heart,
this whole place
comes to a halt,
so, we're just trying to
get out in front of this.
After his last breakup,
he ate 40,000 calories
in three hours.
Right, Pam?
That's what Pam told me.
Yeah.
Or, no, well,
l don't know.
l'm sorry.
l was up all night
with Cece.
Otherwise l'd be
running this.
That's okay.
You probably shouldn't
keep a baby up that late.
We have Mr. Bean
playing in
the conference room,
and the Pink Panther
movie in his office.
With half hour shifts
to watch with him.
And we need bodies
in both these rooms,
people.
So, please sign up.
He's coming.
PAM: Oh. Okay.
Everyone, remember
when he gets like this,
he will wallow
if you empathize.
Keep conversations light.
And if you get stuck
and you don't know
what to do,
make a random
sound effect.
Okay, farting noise,
whatever. Okay.
Hey, everyone.
No, out.
DWlGHT: Get out, right now.
Leave now.
DWlGHT:
Get out. Right now.
PAM:
Please, please!
And if he makes a joke,
just laugh it up
no matter what, okay?
Morning, everyone.
ALL: Hey!
Hey!
Hello.
Michael,
nice tie or something.
Thank you.
lt's reversible, l think.
(ALL LAUGHlNG)
That's hilarious.
PAM:
That's awesome.
You want some ice cream?
Oh ! Wow. Are those
Eagles flavors?
"Cake lt To The Limit,"
that's my favorite.
l love that.
Too much for me to
have by myself.
Anybody want to share?
(lMlTATES BALL BOUNClNG)
Okay, well. . . That's random.
l will dig into those later.
l don't follow this
exactly.
"The descendents
of any replicants
"from this union
shall have. . ."
Joint custody.
Are we talking about
your grandchildren?
No.
Rather than spend
all day in court,
we have decided to
settle our dispute
using a mediator.
lt was an option
spelled out in our
child-rearing contract.
Alleged contract.
Alleged?
l'm going to own your farm
by the time this is over.
Pfft. Yeah, just try.
l will do legal jujitsu
on you.
Yeah.
(EXCLAlMlNG)
See, don't even
need to make contact.
The law will do it.
So much of this is
just impossible to verify.
ltem five, point B,
the beet juice cleanse.
l'm doing it.
You know l am.
lt's disgusting.
How do we know this?
l'd like to see
a stool sample.
Dwight, look at my teeth.
Ugh !
ANDY: No secret crying.
Hasn't even opened
the tissue box in there.
Could he still be seeing her?
l don't think he'd do that.
So, we're gonna say
the most likely scenario
is that Michael
matured overnight?
lt happened to
Tom Hanks in Big.
Exactly.
lt happened in Big.
No, l gotta go.
Text me later.
l'm really too
tired to do this.
Me, too.
Then let's just not do this.
Do you have any idea
of the risks involved?
Hey, Michael.
Hey.
We were wondering
if you'd like to have
dinner with us tonight
in our home and
play with our baby?
We could order in
from Hooters.
Hooters to go, nice.
We can watch a movie
and play Rock Band.
Billy Joel Rock Band.
That exists?
Yes.
Okay, well, l'll have to
take a rain check,
but thanks for the offer.
Michael Scott,
are you still seeing Donna?
MlCHAEL: Okay, Pam,
she's not invisible,
so stop asking
silly questions.
Michael.
Since when is this an office
where we delve into
each other's personal lives?
l like Donna.
ls it wrong to
keep seeing her?
Depends on who you ask.
l mean,
if you ask her husband
or you took a random poll,
yeah, it's wrong.
That is something
l would never do.
Well,
l think we all know what
you're capable of, Meredith.
Hey, l have never cheated on,
been cheated on
or been used to cheat with.
l ask everyone in the room,
"Are you in a relationship?"
People, this is Scranton
and many people
consider that to be
the Paris of
northeastern Pennsylvania.
And in Paris,
it is rude for a woman to
have less than four lovers.
Ugh ! Ryan, l do not
want you hanging out
with Michael anymore.
Okay.
Okay, l will have you know
that l asked Donna about this
and she is fine with it.
And just to be sure,
l asked her again afterward,
same answer.
How does he feel about it?
He is never gonna find out.
He is a high school
baseball coach,
he wakes up early,
he goes to bed early.
Look at how long it took
for him to find out.
lt was right under his nose.
l had to tell him.
Okay, now you're
just being hurtful.
l'm sorry.
Why is it okay
for Stanley to cheat?
Or for Phyllis to cheat?
Hey.
On her diet.
He's a sports guy.
He's scummy.
Dog fighting,
drugs, they spit.
Did Donna tell you that?
ReaI Sports with
Bryant Gumball.
So, you're just
making a giant assumption.
You don't even know the guy.
You know what?
l am declaring
a moment of silence
right now.
Ten minutes of silence
honoring Michael Jackson.
Just sit there
and think about
Michael Jackson.
My name's Andy Bernard
and l am a cuckold.
For those of you unfamiliar
with William Shakespeare,
a cuckold is
a man whose woman
is cheating on him.
l've lived the part.
And let me tell you,
l would so much rather
play the part on stage.
So, here's the thing
about infidelity.
No, no.
When are you people
going to stop
casting the first stone?
l am not in the wrong here.
l am the good guy.
How does that work?
Do you think this husband
is a super sweet, nice guy?
Do you think he's an angel?
l don't think so.
Why is his wife going off
and having a little
something-something with me?
There has to be
a problem with him.
ln any cheating movie,
the person getting
cheated on is the hero.
You're Ali Larter,
l'm Beyoncé.
l am Beyoncé always.
Not this time.
Yes, l am.
This guy's a high school
baseball coach, right?
Let's go check him out,
see what
a horrible person he is.
l would love that.
Yeah.
Those teams have games
and practices every day.
Let's go check it out.
l have work to do.
Really?
l thought you were the boss.
Let's go.
l can't wait to see
this jerk who is making me
cheat on his wife.
l should punch him
in the nose
for what he's
making me do to her.
(PEOPLE CHEERlNG)
(ANDY VOCALlZlNG)
All right, Andy, please.
Baseball !
Shh !
Try not to draw attention,
please.
That's him. That's him.
Where?
Right there.
The coach.
Stage right or stage left?
l played batboy
in Damn Yankees.
Right there. Look, look.
Follow my finger, okay? See?
The grownup by the base.
And now coaching third base
with two arms, two legs
and a heart capable
of feeling pain. . .
All right.
Can you just. . .
. . .is number. . .
Can you just act normal
for a second, please?
Whatever.
l'm the one blending in.
(SNORlNG)
(CLEARlNG THROAT)
(PAM CONTlNUES SNORlNG)
Guys?
Pam?
Hey. Oh ! Hi, Gabe.
Can you two please
join me in my office?
Now.
You were supposed
to be the lookout.
Yeah, well,
it's really warm in here.
lt's like a sleeping bag.
l don't want to
be the heavy here,
but honestly, guys,
this makes us all look bad.
Sorry about that.
So embarrassing.
Good, okay,
end of the dressing down.
l just hate that part
of the job, you know?
The power dynamic.
Well, you were
surprisingly restrained.
We will be well
rested tomorrow.
Okay. That's great, actually,
because l wanted
to talk to you
about something else.
Excellent. Go for it.
l'm sure you got my e-mail
about the printer fires,
the one with
the branching decision tree.
l actually
designed that chart.
Kind of hoping
it catches on.
Anyway, the question is,
what is the best
way to disseminate
important information
in an efficient way?
Right. So let's. . .
Finally, there's
a provision here
in the occurrence
that the child is
born an old man,
à la Benjamin Button.
Same page.
Go to the next one.
Same page. We're fine there.
Just keep moving.
Despite
the provision covering
whether this is all
part of The Matrix. . .
Which we can't know. . .
. . .this is essentially. . .
. . .unless we're unplugged. . .
. . .equivalent to a donor
or surrogate contract. . .
. . .and wake up in the future.
. . .which is
actually pretty common.
So, l have to tell you
that this is
a solid contract.
What?
Look, l can't enforce
that anybody have a child
with anyone else.
What?
MEDlATOR: So essentially
this comes down to damages.
Now, there is some precedence
for the range of $30,000.
What?
l don't have
$30,000 lying around.
l have it buried very deeply,
and l don't want to dig past
a certain someone to get it.
Chase Dixon is up,
could be a big play.
You have no idea what
you're talking about.
l know it's like cricket.
No. No.
Well, home plate
is like a wicket.
You don't know,
you don't know anything.
Look at him.
Look at him over there.
High fiving?
He didn't even do anything.
The kid did all the work.
l bet he does that at home.
l bet it's like, "Hey,
Donna, why don't you
wash the dishes?
"High five, Donna."
"Hey, why don't you bring
me my slippers? High five.
l'm taking all the credit."
He seems pretty
well liked by the team.
Okay, well, that's because
he's paying their salary.
You do know
that high school coaches
don't pay their players.
l know. l know. l know.
That was a euphemism.
$30,000?
There's got to be another way.
He has a 60-acre beet farm
that is worth
a small fortune.
Look, l will not pay.
Well, l have an alternative.
"lntercourse to completion
five individual times
"rendered at my discretion."
Look, l don't think
that's actually legal.
Agreed.
Five times for $30,000?
Not a bad stud fee.
Better than most horses.
But not on your bed.
lt's lumpy.
Those lumps are cats,
and those cats have names,
and those names
are Amber, Milky Way,
Dianne and Lumpy.
Fine, five times.
Look, l can't legally
watch this unfold.
lt's coming
a little dangerously
close to prostitution.
l want eye contact.
No.
Yes.
Do you understand how rare
that is in nature?
l'm not some farm animal.
ANDY: Great game, Coach.
Shh.
Okay, all right,
don't, don't, don't.
You guys are awesome.
Best game l've
ever seen in my life.
Yeah, right.
You must be rooting
for the other guys.
Ha! The other guys
can go die.
Okay.
Baseball !
Go talk to him.
No, God,
you go talk to him.
Shane, great game, man.
Do l know you?
No, just big fans.
Both of us.
Are you somebody's
parents?
Are you guys Kenny's dads?
(LAUGHS) No, no,
but we're gay for baseball.
Okay.
But l have a wife, actually,
who l really love a lot.
Yeah.
Okay.
Let's go!
l am so into
the institution
of marriage.
lsn't marriage the best,
you know?
Two good people
finding each other,
getting all committed to
each other.
You love baseball,
what else do you love?
Let's round you out
as a person.
Hey, l'm really sorry,
l'm just trying to
focus here on the game.
l get it, man. l love it.
That's what
makes you a good coach.
You know, but as a fan,
it just helps me
enjoy the game better
if l know
the coach loves his wife.
Of course. Okay,
l've got to
get back to this.
Of course.
All right.
But real quick,
l want you to meet
my associate. Sheldon !
No, no, no. l'm good.
ANDY: Come on, get over here.
ANDY: Get over here.
Oh, my God. All right.
Sheldon, say hi
to the nice coach.
Sorry, l've got
some stomach cramps.
SHANE: lt's all right,
it's all right,
just keep it going.
Well, that was not at all
what l expected.
(LAUGHS lN RELlEF)
My heart's still racing.
I just looked
a man in the eyes
and I shook his hand.
All the time I was thinking,
"I'm sleeping with your wife."
You know who does that?
James freaking Bond.
Okay, orange slices.
There you go.
Thanks, Michael.
Don't thank me,
thank Dylan's mom.
There you go.
(MlCHAEL LAUGHlNG)
Why would you throw
something wet at me?
MlCHAEL: You love it.
There you go.
Now, were those
for the team?
No. They didn't say "team,"
they just said "Coal Hawks."
l don't think those
were yours to take.
Well, then, it wouldn't
be the first time
l stole something
away from Coach Shane.
ANDY: l just want to
go on record as saying
that l do not
condone this affair.
And l even went
so far as to
force Michael
to confront
the victim of his behavior.
Did you talk to him?
l did.
You talked to the man
whose wife you're
having an affair with?
Wow, that is crazy.
Was there a fist fight?
No, we just talked.
He's very nice.
And it didn't
change your mind?
lt did not.
Michael, that's awful.
lsn't it?
PHYLLlS: Yes.
l'm awful, aren't l?
Yeah, that's pretty. . .
l'm an awful guy. Ooh !
How can you
live with yourself?
l am what l am, Oscar.
And l want what l want.
And right now
l want a piece of cake.
From now on, when l'm hungry,
l am going to eat
whatever l am hungry for.
That is
a dangerous game, friend-o.
Well, because
l thought that it was
a book about Anthropologie,
the store.
l don't know why
you were in that
part of the bookstore.
Because it's next to
the baby section, okay?
Well, that makes more sense.
You should have
said that at the beginning,
when you said,
"l read a book
about anthropology."
KELLY: l don't even know
why you're screaming
at me right now.
l'm not screaming.
That's Meredith's cake.
lt's her birthday.
l don't care.
l have an appetite for life.
Mmm.
God, that's lemon.
Good for you, man.
Good for you.
He takes what he wants.
You know what?
l think you're attractive
and l want to sleep with you.
What about Kelly?
You read my mind.
ls this a joke?
Yep.
lt's hard to
live that way, man.
You gotta really not care
what people think
about you, right?
l don't know how
you do it, Michael.
l can't be that cold.
You'll learn, baby,
you'll learn.
DWlGHT: I am
an honorabIe man and
I wiII honor the contract.
But l don't have to
give her the good stuff.
Schrute sperm are strong,
but they're no match
for a grown Schrute man.
(SCREAMlNG)
(CHUCKLES)
Let's see what she gets.
(SCREAMlNG)
Boss, we're out of paper.
Yeah, l noticed that.
Aren't you
gonna add any more?
Nope.
He don't give
an F about nothing.
l have got big balls.
l don't think
l'm gonna make it.
(YAWNlNG) What about
an energy drink
or something?
lt gets in the breast milk.
lf l drink it, Cece drinks it
six hours later.
Well, it doesn't mean
l can't drink it.
Well, it does and it doesn't.
l probably
shouldn't tell you this,
but a lot guys
in the warehouse
work multiple jobs,
so we have a place.
A place?
A restful location.
Talk to Glen, he'll
take you up in the lift.
You sleep in the warehouse?
Light bulb's burned out,
so it's dark.
And the heat
from the backup generator
keeps it nice and warm.
Sometimes l think about it
when l'm trying to
fall asleep at home.
But as far as
the rest of the office goes,
it doesn't exist. Okay?
Okay.
Pam?
For your signature.
Okay.
Phyllis?
Okay, look at me.
Phyllis, look at. . .
Okay, that's. . .
All right, all right,
you know what?
l'm sick of this.
l'm sick of the little
disapproving head shakes.
lf you think
that's going to have
any effect on me,
it will not.
l am going to leave
right now and go to
a motel to meet Donna.
Why not your condo?
Because a motel is dirty,
and it is sexy.
Like me and like Donna.
And frankly,
the stuff that we're into
isn't very condo-appropriate.
Michael, will you drop it?
Everybody's spoken their mind
and no one's
changing their mind.
Okay, Morgan Freeman
narrating everything.
Do you want
someone to stop you?
Because no one's going to.
Nobody better try to stop me.
Good.
l could have stopped him.
(CAR LOCK BEEPlNG)
Are you warmed up?
No.
God, Angela,
why is that always
my responsibility?
ANGELA: What did you
do to yourself?
DWlGHT: Never mind.
Just. . . Never mind.
ANGELA:
Well, it better work.
DWlGHT: lt'll work.
Stop kissing me.
(ANGELA SCOFFlNG)
lt's not in the contract.
MlCHAEL: How do I feeI about
breaking up with Donna?
Good. MoraI.
I feel proud.
Like a grown-up.
(CELL PHONE BEEPlNG)
That was not easy
because I really
Iiked her a Iot.
I'm a IittIe bit
emotional right now
because I know
that I absolutely
made the right decision.
At the end of the day,
we have to do what's right.
And it was either
living with myself
or being happy.
And l picked
the
former.
Michael Scott?
Yes?
Do you want to make
a comment on the rumors?
(SlGHlNG) Um. . .
l have done some
very bad things.
Things of which
l'm not proud.
l would like to
publicly apologize
to the coach
and the players,
and l vow to never
listen to
my bodily instincts
ever again.
l'm talking about
the Sabre printers
that catch on fire.
Oh ! Okay,
l was talking about. . .
What's going on?